[music]
>> Welcome to 2026 release wave one launch
edition of Business Central. This
session is about enhanced demo data.
So basically there's only one value of
this, of course, it's just when you do
your demos that all reports and Power BI
just showcase a case a story and that's
what we're trying to to do just make the
demo data in a way where where these
reports kind of give some insights.
Uh so we are have added demo data across
fixed assets, sales, purchasing, and
subscription billing. So let's just see
a few examples of that. Everything by
the way is part of the demo data control
tool under analytics. So you just
install that and you get these goodies.
For fixed assets, we added transaction
data for acquisitions and depreciations.
And when we have that, you can now demo
all the reports that we added in version
25 as well as analysis mode on fixed
asset ledgers and FA fixed asset
registers. So all of those demos now
light up
using because we have you now have demo
data.
In the areas of sales purchasing, we
took the approach that we wanted to make
it
easier or better to demo the Power BI
apps. So that means both we added more
document demo data, but we also spread
it or made more variation in the in the
in the demo data. Spread it documents
across sales people, added discounts,
adding a new purchasing department
dimension, and purchases. And when we do
all of this, when you post documents
having this demo data,
there's an added benefit that also in
finance
things are coming in the finance in the
general ledger through the
through these documents so so simply
getting so so the the demo experience
even in finance is is improved by these
changes.
For open sales orders, we added 11 more.
So for back orders, also nine more, I
think.
Purchase return orders, we didn't have
any, so now you have at least some. That
just
makes it just easier to to to demo
things where if you actually have demo
data, you don't have to set it up.
With subscription billing,
we added both master data and
transactions and that lights up all the
analysis mode in inside the client as
well as the Power BI app for
subscription billing.
So we added more customer contracts, we
added more vendor contracts, and we
added more billing lines. And these
screenshots you can see instead of
showcasing Power BI app, I'm just
showcasing
the the the other way of demoing or
having reports in Business Central,
which is uh taking lists into analysis
mode.
If you want to learn more about the demo
tool, there's a link down here both on
screen but also in the description. If
you want to extend the demo data tool to
to other scenarios, that's possible.
Um and for if you're interested in demo
data, you might probably also interested
in other types of analytics. So we have
a ton of breakout sessions around that
linked down here in the description. Uh
sales, inventory, finance analytics,
financial reporting, subscription
billing, Power BI Excel, and analysis
mode. So check that out. We hope that
you will like it all.
And with that, that concludes this
session on
demo data. There's a ton of other
resources that you can learn about here
after I say goodbye. So thanks and I
hope you watch all the other sessions in
the launch edition. Thank you.
We have compiled a number of general
resources that we believe are key both
for partners but also Business Central
customers. Most Some of these are
partner, some of them are also for
customers. So the first one is
called aka.ms/bcall.
This is a partner resource for that
contains lists of every other aka link
that is needed for you to understand
anything about both the Business Central
product but also processes around it.
We call these aka links because they are
called aka.ms and then for for
something. And with Business Central
links, we all always prefix with BC and
then something.
The next one is our partner network
social media for for Business Central
partners, Viva Viva Engage. So
aka.ms/bcvivaengage
is where you go and interact with other
partners. It's not open for customers.
This is where you can ask questions,
interact with the product group,
interact with with with each other
in a in a closed network.
Second link a third link is for both
partners and customers. We are called
office hours. So office hours is
something we do once or twice a month
from the product group engaging with the
community about new features or things
we want to discuss. aka.ms/bcofficehours
is the is the place where you go to find
out about upcoming events.
These are recorded. I believe the
recordings are available only to
partners, but the live events are
available to customers as well.
Fourth link is YouTube our YouTube
channel. I'll talk about that
in the next slide and link in in the
next slide.
And then finally for for Microsoft
partners, the BC's
aka.ms/bcpartnerportal
is where you get a lot of the resources
as a partner such as compete decks,
pitch decks, and a lot of other
resources.
For LinkedIn, this is our product
group's LinkedIn profile. We have 30K or
more followers. So both partners and
customers. This is the place where we
from the product group put in news and
small bits of information outside the
quote unquote official channel. So
follow us on LinkedIn to learn what's
happening right now
in in this in the around the product.
Um and then
also on our YouTube channel where this
is where you're probably watching this
aka.ms/bcyoutube.
We put in not only these launch editions
twice a year but also
co-pilot and AI video shorts, tips and
tricks, technical deep dives, under the
hood.
We even have this what's cooking where
we put little nuggets of of videos out
for new features that are even coming in
on the YouTube channel before
they're coming in the release notes. So
watch
and maybe bookmark us on YouTube. And
also notice all the playlists. So
the content is also organized in areas,
not only all the videos. So if you have
an area that has special interest such
as analytics,
you can find an
a playlist and kind of see all the
content related to that.
And that's it. That is truly it. We
won't
There will be no more. So thank you for
watching all the way to the end. And
again, have a great day. Thank you.